Next, we will announce the results.
[ﾃﾚﾋﾞ]ﾗﾝｷﾝｸﾞの発表です 第５位は…
In fifth, we have this little puppy.
(住子)
ｶﾜｲｲわね みんなは 犬派 猫派？
Oh, how cute.
Are you all dog lovers or cat lovers?
(宇佐)やっぱ 犬かなあ
(シロ)俺は 断然 猫だねえ
I'm more of a dog person.
I'm a total cat person!
できれば 俺を
すごーく嫌っててほしいなあ
I like it best when they really hate my guts,
でも時々は 気まぐれに近づいて
期待を思い切りぶち壊して
but occasionally approach me,
only to dash my hopes as if to say, "Serves you right, meow!"
ざまみろだﾆｬｰﾝとかって…
河合荘って ﾍﾟｯﾄOKなんですか？
Are pets allowed at the Kawai Complex?
ダメって決めてはないけど
There isn't a rule banning them.
(麻弓)私は絶対飼わないぞー！
何すか いきなり!?
I'm never gonna have a pet!
Where'd that come from?!
独身がﾍﾟｯﾄ飼ったら 満たされて
もう立ち向かえなくなるんだ…
When a single person gets a pet, they end up content with it,
この ｢私は独り｣って現実とな…
and can no longer face the reality
that they are still alone!
(彩花)そうかなあ… 麻弓さんは
ﾍﾟｯﾄ 飼った方がいいと思うけど
Are you sure about that?
I think you should get a pet.
えッ？
(彩花)多少 飢えを満たせば➡
Huh?
If you felt a little more content,
もっと冷静に
男選び できるんじゃない？
maybe you'd stop jumping every man you see.
Episode Eleven
I Don't Have Any Friends
A pet, huh...
ペットか… 飼うなら犬だけど
If I had a pet, I'd want a dog,
散歩がなあ…
じゃあ ｳｻｷﾞは？➡
but I wouldn't want to walk it...
What about a rabbit?
お友達が飼ってるんだけど
すっごくｶﾜｲｲわよ
One of my friends has a pet rabbit and it's absolutely adorable!
ｳｻｷﾞかあ… いいかも！
A rabbit, huh?
That could work!
If I feel content, maybe I can find a good man.
満たされれば いい男が…
Sorry, Mayumi-san.
麻弓さん ｺﾞﾒﾝ
やっぱり彩花 反対
I'm against this, after all.
はあッ!?
満たされて冷静になった頃に
Huh?
I forgot that it's more crucial to consider
選ぶほどの男が残ってるかの方が
重要なの 忘れてて
whether you'll have any men left to choose from by the time you feel content.
You know, since I'm never short on options.
ほら 彩花 選びたい放題だから
I'll kill you!
Uh,
あの… 先輩は 犬派っすか？
それとも 猫？
are you a dog person, Senpai?
Or more of a cat person?
(律)あッ… どっちも好き
そうっすか…
I like both.
Oh...
<ああ… 何か こないだから
ｷﾞｸｼｬｸしてんなあ 何でだ？>
It's been kind of awkward between us since that incident.
Why?
(住子)律ちゃん 前に
大型犬が好きって言ってたわよね
Rit-chan,
you once mentioned that you like big dogs, right?
Oh... Yeah.
えッ？ ああ…
あッ そうなんだ
Really? Like Labs?
ラブとか？
うん…
Yeah.
Our neighbor Yamada-san had a—
昔 うちの近所の山田さん…
Hey, Usa-kun is kinda like a big dog, right?
あ～ッ
宇佐君って 大型犬っぽいよね
うッ…
えッ… 何…
Huh?
What...
Not in the least!
全然！ ぽくない！
えッ…
I love
big dogs
Usa isn't
like one
Don't think you can stand
on equal footing with them
ウフッ… うん
You haven't even
copulated yet
Gross
曲解すなッ！
I love
big dogs
Usa isn't
like one
Don't think you can stand
on equal footing with them
You haven't even
copulated yet
Gross
Usa isn't
like one
Don't think you can stand
on equal footing with them
You haven't even
copulated yet
Gross
Don't twist her words!
Usa isn't
like one
Don't think you can stand
on equal footing with them
You haven't even
copulated yet
Gross
Usa isn't
like one
Don't think you can stand
on equal footing with them
You haven't even
copulated yet
Gross
Don't think you can stand
on equal footing with them
You haven't even
copulated yet
Gross
Don't think you can stand
on equal footing with them
You haven't even
copulated yet
Gross
Don't think you can stand
on equal footing with them
You haven't even
copulated yet
Gross
Don't think you can stand
on equal footing with them
You haven't even
copulated yet
Gross
Don't think you can stand
on equal footing with them
You haven't even
copulated yet
Gross
Don't think you can stand
on equal footing with them
You haven't even
copulated yet
Gross
Don't think you can stand
on equal footing with them
You haven't even
copulated yet
Gross
Don't think you can stand
on equal footing with them
You haven't even
copulated yet
Gross
Don't think you can stand
on equal footing with them
You haven't even
copulated yet
Gross
Don't think you can stand
on equal footing with them
You haven't even
copulated yet
Gross
Don't think you can stand
on equal footing with them
You haven't even
copulated yet
Gross
Don't think you can stand
on equal footing with them
You haven't even
copulated yet
Gross
Don't think you can stand
on equal footing with them
You haven't even
copulated yet
Gross
Don't think you can stand
on equal footing with them
You haven't even
copulated yet
Gross
Don't think you can stand
on equal footing with them
You haven't even
copulated yet
Gross
Don't think you can stand
on equal footing with them
You haven't even
copulated yet
Gross
Don't think you can stand
on equal footing with them
You haven't even
copulated yet
Gross
Don't think you can stand
on equal footing with them
You haven't even
copulated yet
Gross
Don't think you can stand
on equal footing with them
You haven't even
copulated yet
Gross
Don't think you can stand
on equal footing with them
You haven't even
copulated yet
Gross
Don't think you can stand
on equal footing with them
You haven't even
copulated yet
Gross
Don't think you can stand
on equal footing with them
You haven't even
copulated yet
Gross
Don't think you can stand
on equal footing with them
You haven't even
copulated yet
Gross
Don't think you can stand
on equal footing with them
You haven't even
copulated yet
Gross
Don't think you can stand
on equal footing with them
You haven't even
copulated yet
Gross
Don't think you can stand
on equal footing with them
You haven't even
copulated yet
Gross
Don't think you can stand
on equal footing with them
You haven't even
copulated yet
Gross
Don't think you can stand
on equal footing with them
You haven't even
copulated yet
Gross
Don't think you can stand
on equal footing with them
You haven't even
copulated yet
Gross
I thought
there might
be some
fun to be
had here,
and there
sure was!
I thought
there might
be some
fun to be
had here,
and there
sure was!
I was just saying what I thought.
思ったことを言っただけなのに…
You're broadcasting your true motive to the world!
本音漏れてるってﾚﾍﾞﾙじゃ
ないっすけど！
意識されてるってことじゃない？
本音！
At least you got her attention, right?
But not in
a good way
There it is again!
あながち 間違ってないかもよ
そうかな？
She might not be wholly wrong, though.
Really?
Don't you think the word "wholly" sounds dirty?
｢あながち｣って 何かエロいよね
Rust away.
こういうとき お前が性格悪くて
よかったって思うぞ
Moments like these are when I'm
glad you're such a nasty person.
<せっかく
普通に話せそうだったのに>
I was so close to having a normal conversation with her...
<仕返ししたくても
彩花さんって弱点が…>
And I can't retaliate because I don't know any of Sayaka-san's weaknesses...
Excuse me!
≪(美晴)すみませーん！
常田美晴と申しますが➡
My name is Tsuneda Miharu!
Does Watanabe Sayaka-san live here?
こちらに 渡辺彩花さんは…
≪(彩花)常子!?
(美晴)あッ ナベちゃん
Tsuneko?!
Oh, Nabe-chan.
暑くて えらかった～
何で ここに!?
It's so hot outside.
What are you doing here?!
≪(美晴)明日 こっちの方で
高校の集まりがあるんやって
There's a high school reunion in the area tomorrow.
せっかくやし ナベちゃんの下宿先
見てみたくって
So I figured I'd see where you're living right now.
Okay, you've seen it.
はい 見たね じゃ 帰ろっか
うん 今日 泊めて～
Time to go now!
Oh, can I spend the night?
話 聞け！
つか いきなり 泊まりって…
Listen to me!
And you can't ask to spend the night out of nowhere!
But if I'd asked first, you would've said no.
だって
先に言ったら 断るやろ？
住所 教えてくれへんから
おばさんに聞いたんやよ
You wouldn't tell me your address, so I had to ask your mom.
N-Nabe-chan!
彩花ちゃんのお友達なんて
初めて！
This is the first time I've met one of Sayaka-chan's friends!
Please come in!
上がって 上がって
(彩花)ちょっと…
Wait!
Nabe-chan's room is over there!
ナベちゃんのお部屋は
あっちで～す １名様 河合荘…
Welcome to the Kawai Complex!
Sayaka-san actually has a friend...
<彩花さん 友達いたんだ…>
Thank you very much!
And she's nothing like her...
It's no trouble at all.
あッ… あのクギバット➡
That nail bat...
ナベちゃんが
中学時代 使っとったやつだ➡
It's the one Nabe-chan used in middle school.
That brings back memories.
懐かしいねえ…
What? She actually used that thing?
<マジで使ってたのか…>
ああ ｢人に｣じゃないでね
Oh, she didn't use it on people.
She just used it to destroy a shed.
農具小屋を破壊するときに
使っとっただけ
A shed?
農具小屋？
悪さして よく閉じ込められ…
They used to lock her up in it as punishment for—
Oh, dear. Tsuneda-san has some bizarre dreams.
や～だ～ 常田さんったら
ﾏﾆｱｯｸな夢 見ちゃって
現実と混同しちゃったの？
Are you mixing them up with reality?
I detect the faint scent of a kindred spirit!
それって そこはかとなく
同士の匂いがするんだけど
Comrade
黙ってろ
Keep quiet.
(シロ)ツネちゃんの荷物は
彩花ちゃんの部屋に持っていく？
Should I take Tsune-chan's belongings to Sayaka-san's room?
What?
I never agreed to let her stay!
(彩花)泊めるなんて言ってないし
部屋 散らかってて 狭いし！
And my room's a mess, so there's no space!
I don't mind if there's a bunch of homo manga lying around.
ホモ漫画 いっぱいでも
気にならんよ
Wow, Tsuneda-san, your bumpkin dialect is showing.
やだ～ 常田さん 方言 キツい
こっちでは それ
｢ぬいぐるみ｣って言うんだよ～
We call those "stuffed animals" here in the city.
H-Homo manga?
ぬいぐるみって意味だけど 何か？
She means stuffed animals. Got a problem?
(美晴)
ごめん 言い方 悪かったね➡
Sorry, I should have put it a different way.
I'm talking about manga where men engage
男の人と 男の人が
情熱的に愛し合ってる漫画
in passionate acts of love with other men.
Okay, time for you to shut up!
うん ちょっと お前
お黙ろうか…
Th-This person
<こ… この人…>
is like a whole box of Sayaka's weaknesses!
<彩花さんの弱点ﾎﾞｯｸｽだ！>
Come inside. You must be tired, so let's sit in the living room.
さあさあ お疲れでしょうし
居間へ どうぞ
酒でも飲んで
ナベちゃん話 しましょうよ
Let's have a drink and hear some stories about Nabe-chan.
Hey! I said go home!
(彩花)ちょっと 帰れってば！
(美晴)で みんなから 私ら
So, everybody called us Nabe-Tsune.
ﾅﾍﾞﾂﾈって 呼ばれとったよね～
ﾅﾍﾞﾂﾈ！
Nabe-Tsune!
Sounds like someone who'd give you a piece of his mind!
言いたいこと言いそう
幼なじみってやつっすか？
So are you childhood friends?
(美晴)う～ん 中２からやで
どうなんやろ？
Well, we met in our second year of middle school...
Some plumb nasty upperclassmen were giving me a hard time,
でえ～れｲｼﾞﾜﾙな先輩に
からまれて 困っとったときに
Mighty
-
Really
Mighty
-
Really
Mighty
-
Really
Mighty
-
Really
Mighty
-
Really
Mighty
-
Really
Mighty
-
Really
Mighty
-
Really
Mighty
-
Really
Mighty
-
Really
Mighty
-
Really
Mighty
-
Really
Mighty
-
Really
Mighty
-
Really
Mighty
-
Really
Mighty
-
Really
Mighty
-
Really
Mighty
-
Really
Mighty
-
Really
Mighty
-
Really
Mighty
-
Really
Mighty
-
Really
Mighty
-
Really
Mighty
-
Really
Mighty
-
Really
Mighty
-
Really
Mighty
-
Really
Mighty
-
Really
Mighty
-
Really
Mighty
-
Really
Mighty
-
Really
Mighty
-
Really
Mighty
-
Really
Mighty
-
Really
Mighty
-
Really
Mighty
-
Really
Mighty
-
Really
Mighty
-
Really
Mighty
-
Really
Mighty
-
Really
Mighty
-
Really
Mighty
-
Really
Mighty
-
Really
Mighty
-
Really
Mighty
-
Really
Mighty
-
Really
Mighty
-
Really
Mighty
-
Really
ナベちゃんに助けてもらって…
ちょっと待て
and Nabe-chan saved me.
Hold on.
彩花をいじれるネタは大歓迎だが
I'm all for stories I can use to make fun of Sayaka,
｢ﾎﾝﾄは いいやつ｣ｴﾋﾟｿｰﾄﾞとか
全然 求めてねえから
but I don't want hear any stories that make her sound good.
Don't worry.
(美晴)大丈夫 正しくは➡
What actually happened was that the upperclassman got scared and ran
農具小屋から脱出したての
ナベちゃん 見て➡
after seeing Nabe-chan escape from the shed.
先輩が 勝手にビビッて
逃げてっただけだから
Oh, Watanabe
Who are
you, again?
Sayaka Block
Who are
you, again?
Sayaka Block
Who are
you, again?
Sayaka Block
Who are
you, again?
Sayaka Block
Who are
you, again?
Sayaka Block
Who are
you, again?
Sayaka Block
Who are
you, again?
Sayaka Block
Who are
you, again?
Sayaka Block
Who are
you, again?
Sayaka Block
Who are
you, again?
Sayaka Block
Who are
you, again?
Sayaka Block
Who are
you, again?
Sayaka Block
Who are
you, again?
Sayaka Block
Who are
you, again?
Sayaka Block
Who are
you, again?
Sayaka Block
Who are
you, again?
Sayaka Block
Who are
you, again?
Sayaka Block
Who are
you, again?
Sayaka Block
Who are
you, again?
Sayaka Block
Who are
you, again?
Sayaka Block
I love how pathetic that turned out to be!
Who are
you, again?
Sayaka Block
Who are
you, again?
Sayaka Block
いいぞ！ そのしょうもなさ！
Who are
you, again?
Sayaka Block
Who are
you, again?
Sayaka Block
Who are
you, again?
Sayaka Block
Who are
you, again?
Sayaka Block
Who are
you, again?
Sayaka Block
Who are
you, again?
Sayaka Block
Who are
you, again?
Sayaka Block
What did you do to get locked up in a shed?
何して 小屋に閉じ込められたの？
僕も お願いしたいんだけど
I want to try the same thing.
さ… 彩花の親 厳しくて
M-My parents were very strict.
You probably did something really evil.
えげつないことでもしたんだろ？
違うよ
Nope.
She took eggs from a relative's chicken coop
親戚の鶏舎から 卵 持ち出して
to make slow-cooked eggs and sell them for 50 yen each.
温泉卵にして １個50円で売ってた
良心価格！
ﾔﾍﾞえ 立派な変ｼｮﾘ物件じゃねえか
A fair price!
Wow, she's totally Freak Show territory!
宇佐 出番だ！
Usa, you're up!
Did this Sayaka face make its debut in high school?
この彩花仮面は高校ﾃﾞﾋﾞｭｰ？
それとも大学？
Or was it in college?
You'll pay for this.
覚えてろよ…
いや 中３んときに 突然➡
No, she suddenly made the change in our third year of middle school.
She said something about how important yearbooks are.
｢卒業ｱﾙﾊﾞﾑは大事だ｣って…
I used to get calls from guys
｢卒アル 見て｣って
よく 男から電話来たりしたわ…
telling me to look at our yearbook.
(彩花)そういう過去の栄光は
今後 毒になる一方だから➡
Dwelling on your glory days will only bring you pain in the future,
思い切って 捨てた方がいいよ
何か言ったか？ ナベちゃん
so you should just forget it.
Did you say something, Nabe-chan?
(彩花)くッ…
うーん それもやけど…
That's part of it,
ネットで
芸能人の今昔画像とか見ると
but I realized how smart Nabe-chan was when I saw
before-and-after pictures of celebrities on the Internet.
ナベちゃんは 賢いなあって
小学校のなら ｢成長過程｣で
ごまかせるもんね
If they bring out grade school pictures, you can blame it on a growth spurt.
You're a genius, Sayaka-chan!
あったまいい！ 彩花ちゃん
≪(美晴)ナベちゃんといると
面白かったなあ 私
I had so much fun when I was with Nabe-chan.
Th-Thank... you...
He looks happy
友達になれて ﾎﾝﾄよかったって
思っとる！
I'm so glad that we became friends!
I'm thinking I made a big mistake.
私は今 失敗したって思ってる
I wish we had gone to the same high school.
高校も
ナベちゃんと一緒がよかったな➡
You ended up going to an all-girls school far away.
ナベちゃん
遠くの女子校 行っちゃうし
What? All-girls school?
えッ 女子校？
似合わねえ…
Hardly a match...
And during breaks, you were busy with your boyfriends and girlfriends and BL...
休みは 彼とか彼女とかＢＬとか
忙しいし
うんッ…
大学は もっと遠くなるし
And then you went to a university that was even further away...
ああ… 明日 やだなあ…
Huh?
I don't want to leave tomorrow...
Did she
just...
Was I hearing
things?
やっと つぶれた
あんまり お酒 強くないのね
She finally knocked herself out.
She doesn't hold her liquor very well.
明日 大丈夫かしら？
Will she be okay tomorrow?
You girls are really close.
(ｼﾛ)ﾎﾝﾄに仲がいいんだね
(彩花)べつに よくないって
We're not that close.
I always thought you didn't have any friends.
友達
絶対いないと思ってたのに
You always said dealing with other girls was a pain.
女同士とか めんどくせえ～ って
(彩花)めんどくさいよ➡
It is a pain.
They don't listen, they're shameless,
人の話 聞かないし
ずうずうしいし➡
しつこいし
う～ッ…
and they never shut up.
だから そういうの…
That's why she's all I can handle of that.
こいつで もう… うんざり
≪(彩花)常子➡
Tsuneko.
常子… 常子！➡
Tsuneko!
Wake up!
起きろ！
う～ん…
(彩花)今日
高校の集まりがあるんでしょ？
You have a high school reunion today, don't you?
でも まだ 早い…
(彩花)ﾒｲｸしてやるから➡
But it's still early...
I'll do your makeup.
どうせ
苦手なやつでもいるんでしょ？
You'll probably run into people you don't want to see, right?
えッ… 何で それ…
分かるっつーの
How did you know?
I just know.
さっさと顔洗って ｼｬｷｯとしてきな
うｯ…
Go wash your face so you'll be good and awake.
１時間や２時間で完成できる
土台じゃないんだし
With your face, this is gonna take more than one or two hours.
ナベちゃん ひどい！
That was harsh, Nabe-chan!
ウフッ…➡
Thank you for having me.
お邪魔しましたー
Who is she?
Who?
Can I come back?
また来ていいかな？
いいわけあるか～
Of course not.
帰ったときは連絡するから
I'll give you a call when I'm back home.
うん！ 待っとるね
Okay.
I'll be waiting.
ﾎﾝﾜｶするところかもしんねえが…
This is supposed to be a touching moment,
Professor Sayaka's
sorcery
is incredible
Professor Sayaka's
sorcery
is incredible
Professor Sayaka's
sorcery
is incredible
あまりの変貌ぶりに
それどころじゃねえな
but it's completely overshadowed by her transformation.
She looks like Hayashi.
But I just went home not long ago,
(彩花)とはいえ
こないだ帰ったばっかだから➡
当分ないけど
え～ッ!?
so it won't be any time soon.
Thanks for carrying my stuff for me.
(美晴)荷物 ありがとね
いえいえ
No problem.
There are mountains nearby. Do any you-know-whats show up?
≪(美晴)山 近いけど
この辺は あれ おったりする？
｢あれ｣？
≪(美晴)ほら ﾅﾍﾞちゃんの苦手な…
You-know-whats?
You know, the ones Nabe-chan is scared of.
Huh?
A Few Days Later
≪(住子)彩花ちゃん➡
Sayaka-chan?
Sayaka-chan, are you awake?
彩花ちゃん 起きてる？
(彩花)う～ん…
何？
(住子)前 言ってた お友達のﾍﾟｯﾄ➡
What is it?
I'm taking care of a pet for the friend I mentioned the other day,
預かったんだけど 彩花ちゃんの
部屋に入っちゃったみたいなの➡
and I think it went inside your room.
長い耳がカワイイ…
うッ!?
It's adorable, with long ears...
≪(彩花)キャーッ！
うッ…
(住子)宇佐君から聞いたときは
まさかと思ったけど➡
I didn't believe Usa-kun when he first told me,
ホントに苦手なのね ウサギ
but you really are scared of rabbits, aren't you?
(彩花)麻弓さんに このこと
言ったら あの手この手で 泣かす
If you tell Mayumi-san about this,
I'll do things to you that will make you cry.
俺… もう… 泣いてます
Uh, I'm already crying.
I learned one of Sayaka-san's weaknesses.
I found Sayaka's
weakness
I gained one more                 of my own
I gained a new weakness.
weakness
I gained one more                 of my own
一体 何を信じれば…
化粧…？ 化粧 怖い…
I gained one more                 of my own
weakness
What am I supposed to believe?
Makeup...
Makeup is scary...
先輩
Senpai?
Senpai.
先輩
うんッ あッ…
I kept calling and you didn't notice.
何回 呼んでも 気づかないし
That book must be really good.
その本
かなりの当たりみたいっすね
It might be the book of the year for me.
今年 一 二を争うかも
へえ～
Oh, is it a heavy read?
重め？
かなり…
Fairly.
無理っすか？
無理っすね
Too much for me?
Way too much.
Are you on library duty, Usa-kun?
宇佐君 図書当番？
えッ!? ええ まあ…
Uh, yeah...
Of course
not
<こうして 二人で帰るなんて…>
When we first met,
<出会った頃は
考えられなかったけど>
I never imagined we'd walk home from school together.
<でも 先輩との距離は>
But the distance between us
<近かったり 遠かったり>
seems to grow and shrink in turn...
You don't mind if I read, do you?
読んでいっても いいよね？
仕方ないっすね
I guess not.
Having said that,
I get to see up-close how she looks when she's absorbed.
<夢中な顔 近くで見れたり…>
あッ… 先輩 赤
Senpai, red light.
先輩 青
Senpai, green light.
And I'm happy to have the chance to touch her back and shoulders.
<肩とか 背中とか 触れるのが>
She's so slender.
<きゃしゃ… だよな>
This reminds me of those summer urges...
<よみがえる夏の欲求…>
We're back.
ただいま～！
よかったー 夕飯 間に合って
Good thing we made it back in time for dinner.
はあｯ？ ｾｸﾊﾗほやほやの上司と
部下みたいな顔して どうした？
Why do you look like an employee and the boss who sexually harasses her?
Huh?!
えッ!? せ… 先輩
S-Senpai? What's—
どう… まさか 俺が触ったから…
Is it because I was touching you?
This book is just so good,
この本が あまりにも面白くて
キツイ展開の泣けるシーンで…
and I got to a heart-wrenching scene...
そんなこったろうと思ったわ
安心の小説オチ
That's what I figured.
It's always book-related.
そんなこったろうと思ったのに
これ？
If you knew, why did you beat me up?
麻弓さんの攻撃は
流れ弾も強烈だね
Stray bullets from Mayumi-san pack a real punch.
もっと流れればいいのに…
I wish more would hit me.
What kind of book is it?
どんな本なの？
時代小説
A historical novel.
Like Onihei?
(住子)鬼平みたいの？
いや ｲｷﾞﾘｽの…
No, this is set in England.
<前に ｢本の説明するの 苦手｣
って言ってたけど>
She once said that she didn't like to talk about books,
<分かる誰かに薦めたり
感想を言い合ったり>
but she seems to enjoy making recommendations
<それは きっと すごく好きで>
and sharing opinions with people who relate.
<俺が もうちょっと読書家で>
If only I were a more experienced reader
<上級ｼﾞｬﾝﾙも
無理せず話せるやつだったら…>
so I could talk to her about more advanced genres...
Stop ogling her and help me put these books away.
(田神)色ボケしてねえで
棚の整理 手伝えよ
(前村)河合さん
昨日も ここ いたよね？➡
Kawai-san, you were here yesterday, weren't you?
教室でも いつも本読んでるし
本 好きなんだね
And you're always reading in the classroom.
You must love books.
Is she Senpai's classmate?
<先輩のクラスメイト？>
I also...
(前村)私も… うん？
Don't get the wrong idea!
<ああッ 違うんです！
無視してるわけじゃなく…>
She's not ignoring you!
<先輩は ホントは…>
It's just that Senpai is...
Tagami-kun!
田神くん！
この本も 棚にしまって！
Put this book back on the shelf!
You're too loud, Usa!
(田神)うるせえよ 宇佐！
一冊 持ってくんのに ｶｰﾄ使うなよ
Don't use the cart for a single book!
That scared me.
ビックリした…
Maemura-san.
前村さん
あッ あのさ…
Say...
I also like to read.
私も 本 好きなんだけど
何か お薦め ない？
Do you have any recommendations?
えッ!?
河合さん いっぱい知ってそうだし
You look like you know a lot about books.
今 読んでるのは どんなの？
What are you reading right now?
U-Um...
あッ… えーと…
I-It's a novel that takes place in England during World War I.
だ… 第一次大戦のｲｷﾞﾘｽが舞台で…
≪(前村)おおッ 軍事もの？
わあ…
Oh, is it a military story?
俺 帰っていい？
Can I go home?
It's more of an ensemble cast story
ある伯爵家にまつわる群像劇
っていうか…
that follows this count's family.
その世界観 ツボかも
上巻 ここにあるよ
That sounds like a setting I'd love.
I-I have the first book here.
私 今 中巻
借りてみる！
I'm on the second book right now.
I'll borrow it, then!
私 いつも恋愛小説ばっかだから
新鮮
I usually read romance novels, so this will be a new experience!
はあッ…
(前村)あッ 私のお薦めはね➡
Oh, I would recommend Senda Naoki's
千田直紀先生の作品で
｢思うは 遠く｣…
Feelings Distant, Bodies Close.
河合さんのお薦め本
面白かったよ
The book you recommended was great!
R-Really?
そ… そう？
(前村)やっぱ あの時代の主従➡
I love the master-servant relationships during that period.
いいよね
大英帝国が きしみだす時代背景も
And the British Empire setting is always great.
ﾌｯﾄﾏﾝとお嬢様が
駆け落ちすればいいのに
I wish the footman and noble lady would elope.
Huh? I don't remember anything like that.
えッ そんな展開 あったっけ？
妄想
I imagined it.
前村さんのお薦めも 感動した
I found the book you recommended very moving.
It's cliché, but great, right?
ベタだけど いいっしょ？
I don't usually read romance.
恋愛小説 新鮮だった
(前村)あッ 次 移動教室だね➡
Oh, we're in a different classroom next period.
一緒に行こうよ
あッ… うん
Let's go together.
O-Okay.
The people in the count's family are crazy!
もう この伯爵家の人間模様が…
S-Senpai is gushing with a high school girl!
<せ… 先輩が女子高生と
ｷｬｯｷｬ ｳﾌﾌしてる>
<いや 先輩もＪＫだけど>
I mean, Senpai's also a high school girl, but...
<ホントに楽しそう…>
She looks like she's having fun...
That's great...
Oh, I have to go.
うわッ！ もう出なきゃ
See you tomorrow, then.
じゃ また明日
河合さんは このあと何かあるの？
Do you have somewhere you need to be?
べつに…
なら 一緒に帰らない？
No.
Let's walk home together, then. Okay?
ねッ？
あッ うん… いいよ
Oh, sure.
Let's go.
行こう 行こう！
My bonding time with Senpai...
There goes my touchy-feely time with Kawai!
-------------
飛び散れ 青春
pervy
There goes my touchy-feely time with Kawai!
-------------
pervy
There goes my touchy-feely time with Kawai!
-------------
pervy
There goes my touchy-feely time with Kawai!
-------------
pervy
Young love can die!
There goes my touchy-feely time with Kawai!
-------------
pervy
There goes my touchy-feely time with Kawai!
-------------
pervy
There goes my touchy-feely time with Kawai!
-------------
pervy
There goes my touchy-feely time with Kawai!
-------------
pervy
There goes my touchy-feely time with Kawai!
-------------
pervy
There goes my touchy-feely time with Kawai!
-------------
pervy
There goes my touchy-feely time with Kawai!
-------------
pervy
There goes my touchy-feely time with Kawai!
-------------
pervy
There goes my touchy-feely time with Kawai!
-------------
pervy
There goes my touchy-feely time with Kawai!
-------------
pervy
There goes my touchy-feely time with Kawai!
-------------
pervy
There goes my touchy-feely time with Kawai!
-------------
pervy
There goes my touchy-feely time with Kawai!
-------------
pervy
人のﾓﾉﾛｰｸﾞに突然 現れるの
やめてもらえますか？
Can you stop popping up in my monologues?
Do you live at home, Kawai-san?
(前村)河合さんって 自宅？
一人暮らし
I live alone.
ていうか 下宿？
え～ッ すごーい！
Actually, it's more like a boarding house.
Wow, cool!
でも 何で？
親が 海外転勤になって
How come?
My mom works overseas.
Your dad, too?
両方とも？
いや お母さん
No, it's just my mom.
What about your dad, then?
お父さんは？
ああ うち 離婚してて
My parents are divorced.
Oh, I see... Sorry.
(前村)あッ そうなんだ… ごめん
ううん べつに
It's okay.
(前村)海外って どこ？
ｱﾒﾘｶ…
Where overseas?
America...
She keeps asking questions...
<すごく追究されるな…>
That's so cool!
You could have gone with her. Why did you stay behind?
Is this normal?
<これが普通だったっけ？>
<宇佐君が あんまり自然に
流してくれたから…>
Usa-kun didn't dwell on this subject...
≪(前村)下宿かあ…
男子 いるの？
A boarding house, huh?
Are there any guys?
うん まあ…
(前村)うわあ～➡
Yeah.
Are you interested in any of them?
好きになっちゃったりとか
ないの？
No!
Absolutely not!
Not happening!
Out of the question!
Never!
<いや べつに つけていたわけじゃ
なくて 帰り道 同じだから>
I'm not following her or anything.
We walk home the same way!
Hey, can I drop by?
ねえ ちょっと寄ってもいい？
興味あるー
I'm really curious now.
Th-There's nothing special about it.
そんな いいものじゃ…
ちょっとだけだって ねッ？
Just a quick look, okay?
So good!
カーッ うんめえッ
仕事帰りの一杯は たまんねえな
Nothing like a beer after a long day at work!
農耕具を使ったﾌﾟﾚｲって
どう思う？ 彩花ちゃん
How do you feel about S&M play using farming tools, Sayaka-chan?
｢私を収穫してください｣
"Please harvest me"?
Or do I just say, "reap me"?
それとも直球で ｢刈って！｣？
農耕具とか彩花 全然分かんなーい
I don't know anything about farming tools.
夜 ﾃﾞｰﾄ前に ｼｬﾜｰ 浴びよっかな
I should take a shower before my date tonight,
and wash off the blood I'm about to beat out of you.
シロさん
血祭りにあげるついでに
いやあ
医者って みんなｲｹﾒﾝなんですかね
Man, are all doctors supposed to be handsome?
そこの旅館から いい男が
ｿﾞﾛｿﾞﾛ出てきたと思ったら
I saw a bunch of studs walking out of an inn,
and it turned out to be a social event for single doctors.
｢独身医師交流会｣ですって
あと 俺… 今 猛烈に
部屋で 誰かを縛りたい気分です
Also, I'm seriously in the mood to tie someone up in my room right now.
Oh? Rit-chan.
あれ？ 律ちゃん
お友達？
Is she your friend?
旅館周辺をなめるように散歩…
キレイな人ばっかだね
We're off to take a walk in the area of that inn.
They're so pretty.
あッ 男子は？ いないの？
Ah, where are the guys?
Aren't they around?
さ… さあ…
N-No idea...
If I went outside right now, it'd definitely get their attention!
(ｼﾛ)これで 出ていけば
つかみは ﾊﾞｯﾁﾘだよねー➡
Usa-kun, are you staying here?
宇佐君 ここにいて いいの？
いいんすよ
I'm fine.
<俺が一緒だなんて きっと先輩は
ｸﾗｽﾒｲﾄに知られたくない>
I'm sure Senpai doesn't want her
classmate to know we live together.
赤外線 送るね
I'll send you my number.
<そういや ｹｲ番もﾒｱﾄﾞも知らない>
Oh, yeah. I don't know her cell number or e-mail.
<しゃべって二日の人に 負けた>
I lost to someone she'd never spoken to until yesterday.
<分かってたけど…>
Not that I didn't know,
but I guess I really mean nothing to Senpai.
<俺って
先輩の何でもないんだな>
Whose phone was that?
今の 誰の？
えッ!? 律ちゃん？
Huh? Rit-chan?!
(彩花)律ちゃんのメル着音
初めて聞いた
I don't think I've ever heard Rit-chan's e-mail ringtone before.
Maemura
It's happening!
The butler showed up!
This guy's just so damn
cool! <3 >_< Anne, the
housekeeper, is really
suspicious and scary.
On the other hand, I was
wrong about the upper
servant. Each character
has a motive, but they
don't show it on the
surface. That adds a lot
of the mystery to the
story. Can't wait to read
more!
ボタン押すの 遅え
うるさい
She's such a slow typer.
Some high
school girl
Quiet!
うん… 送信… っと
And send.
あッ 間違えた…
Ah, I messed up.
A follow-up message?
追加!? あッ…
宇佐 何 見つめてんだよ～？
Usa, what are you staring at?
頬を赤らめつつ
慣れない指を必死に動かし
Her cheeks are flushed as she fumbles with
inexperienced fingers and releases intermittent gasps.
時々 声を漏らす か…
底知れねえな
The imagination of a virgin has no limits.
童貞の妄想力は
麻弓さんの品性は底が浅いのに
As shallow as you are,
there's no limit to how vulgar you can be.
だだっ広すぎますね
｢ヤダ 待って 私 まだだから｣
Now he can't stand
Hold on.
I'm not ready yet.
Now he can't stand
｢まだ 出さないで…｣
メールを
Don't come inside
my inbox.
おしゃべり禁止！
おしゃぶりとか ヤダ もう
You're not allowed to talk!
Oh, gosh! Now you're thinking oral!
こいつー
誰かーッ！
Someone help!
トイレ 行こう
うッ…
Let's hit the restroom!
トイレ行こう
はッ！
Let's hit the restroom.
トイレー！
ひえーッ！
Restroom!
Let's walk home together!
一緒に帰ろう
うん
Maemura
Hey
You're taking a while
to respond.
Am I bothering you?
I just wanted to discuss
things with you...
Maemura
Hey
You're taking a while
to respond.
Am I bothering you?
I just wanted to discuss
things with you...
Maemura
Hey
You're taking a while
to respond.
Am I bothering you?
I just wanted to discuss
things with you...
Maemura
Hey
You're taking a while
to respond.
Am I bothering you?
I just wanted to discuss
things with you...
Maemura
Hey
You're taking a while
to respond.
Am I bothering you?
I just wanted to discuss
things with you...
Maemura
Hey
You're taking a while
to respond.
Am I bothering you?
I just wanted to discuss
things with you...
Maemura
Hey
You're taking a while
to respond.
Am I bothering you?
I just wanted to discuss
things with you...
Maemura
Hey
You're taking a while
to respond.
Am I bothering you?
I just wanted to discuss
things with you...
Maemura
Hey
You're taking a while
to respond.
Am I bothering you?
I just wanted to discuss
things with you...
Maemura
Hey
You're taking a while
to respond.
Am I bothering you?
I just wanted to discuss
things with you...
Maemura
Hey
You're taking a while
to respond.
Am I bothering you?
I just wanted to discuss
things with you...
Maemura
Hey
You're taking a while
to respond.
Am I bothering you?
I just wanted to discuss
things with you...
Maemura
Hey
You're taking a while
to respond.
Am I bothering you?
I just wanted to discuss
things with you...
Maemura
Hey
You're taking a while
to respond.
Am I bothering you?
I just wanted to discuss
things with you...
Maemura
Hey
You're taking a while
to respond.
Am I bothering you?
I just wanted to discuss
things with you...
Maemura
Hey
You're taking a while
to respond.
Am I bothering you?
I just wanted to discuss
things with you...
Maemura
Hey
You're taking a while
to respond.
Am I bothering you?
I just wanted to discuss
things with you...
Maemura
Hey
You're taking a while
to respond.
Am I bothering you?
I just wanted to discuss
things with you...
Let's walk to school together in the morning.
朝も一緒に行こうよ
トイレ 行こう
Let's hit the restroom.
(前村)トイレー！
Restroom!
慣れた手つきで
けだるげに 何度も…
Rapid motions and a lack of enthusiasm. She's experienced.
You shut up!
お静かに！
あんな疲れた様子の律ちゃん 前に
Don't you see how exhausted Rit-chan is?
けだものか お前は
静かにせえ言うとるやろッ
You animal.
I told you to be quiet!
That's the book she considered a possible best of the year,
<今年一 二を争う本が
全然進んでない>
and she's made no progress.
It's okay if this is what Senpai wants,
<先輩が 望んで そうなら
いいんだ>
but...
<でも… でもさ…>
But still...
ねえ 律ちゃん 土曜 暇？
Hey, Rit-chan. Are you free on Saturday?
本好きの集まりがあるんだけど
律ちゃんも一緒に行こうよ
There's a gathering for book lovers.
You should come along.
私 その… 人見知りで…
I'm kinda shy around new people...
It'll be fine.
(前村)大丈夫 みんな すごく
人当たりがいいし➡
They're all nice people.
律ちゃんのこと 話したら
会いたいって➡
When I told them about you, they wanted to meet you.
趣味が同じだから 楽しいって
ねッ？
We all share the same interests, so it'll be lots of fun. Okay?
≪(前村)じゃ 図書館 集合ね
Then, we'll meet in front of the library.
Hello.
どうも…
(Ａ)はじめまして
Nice to meet you.
Heya.
(Ｂ)よろ～
じゃあ 行こうか
Let's go, then.
えッ… 図書館じゃ…
Aren't we going in the library?
(前村)買い出し行って
それから合流すんの
We're going to buy some things, then meet up with the others.
Oh, we can't do any talking in the library,
<ああ 図書館じゃ話せないし
誰かの家とか ｶﾌｪとか…>
so we're going to someone's house or a café?
<(彩花)今の彼とも
そろそろお別れかな…>
It's probably time to break up with my current boyfriend.
≪(彩花)ただいま～
I'm back!
律ちゃん いないね
お友達とお出かけ
Rit-chan isn't here.
She went out with her friend.
じゃあ 駅前で見たの
やっぱ律ちゃんだったんだ…
So that really was Rit-chan I saw by the train station.
えッ!? ｢図書館で女子会｣って…
Huh?
She was meeting some girls at the library...
There were boys in that group.
(彩花)男子もいたよ
それに 場所…
And they were heading towards...
<ああッ… 先輩…>
Senpai...
<それ…>
That's...
(男子Ａ)何飲む？
(女子Ｂ)お酒ダメ？
What do you want to drink?
We can't order alcohol.
(Ａ)俺 ｱﾆｿﾝ 入れよう
(Ｂ)ﾄﾞﾗﾏの歌…
I'm gonna sing an anime song.
I'll sing one from a drama.
ﾀｲﾄﾙ 何だっけ？
(Ｂ)ああ あれね
What was the title?
Oh, I know the one you mean.
A mixer!
Billiards
Karaoke
Darts
Billiards
Karaoke
Darts
Billiards
Karaoke
Darts
<合コンや！ ああッ…>
A
We'll
all
stay
pitiful
tomorrow
shi
ta
mo
bo
ku
ra
wa
mi
n
na
ka
wa
i
so
u
A
What do we do?! Senpai's at a mixer!
Preview
And the next episode is the last one.
先輩が合コンに!?
次は最終回
When did you get here, Senpai?!
How is the next episode the last one?!
先輩 いつの間に!?
次で終わりって どういうこと？
Mayumi-san!
This show isn't allowed to end until I've found happiness!
私が幸せつかむ前に終わるなんて
許さねえ
Please. The show will be running for years, then.
I'll strangle you.
(彩花)それ待ってたら 長寿番組
I get shivers when I think of how this show is going to
(ｼﾛ)住人達が誰一人 幸せに
なることなく最終回なんて➡
end before any of the residents can find happiness!
No! What about me and Senpai?!
最高にｿﾞｸｿﾞｸする結末
いや！ 俺は先輩と…
What about you and Rit-chan?
Uh...
Want it to end with a French kiss or waking up in bed togeth—
ﾍﾞﾛﾁｭｰして終わるか？
ああ 何かﾑｶついてきた
Oh, man, now I'm pissed off.
We could end with Rit-chan shooting Usa-kun down!
(ｼﾛ)律ちゃんが宇佐君を
ﾊﾞｯｻﾘ切って終わるのもｱﾘ
Women are cruel.
Episode Twelve
Wanted To Get Closer
I'm kicking everyone out of the Kawai Complex.
全員 河合荘から永久追放
そんなｴﾝﾃﾞｨﾝｸﾞ!?
That's the ending?!